memedroid.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy policy :) Memedroid

What information do we collect?

We may collect information from you when you visit our website, use our app, create a user account in Memedroid or contact us through our contact form.

When you use Memedroid:

When you visit our website or use our apps we may collect your **Internet Protocol (“IP”) address** or other unique **device identifier(s)** for any device (mobile phone, laptop, etc) that you use to do it, such as an **Advertising ID** that can be used to show you relevant ads. A Device Identifier is a number that can be randomly assigned to your device or received from it when you visit our site or use our app and can be used to identify your device. In addition, we may estimate your device's physical location and other network information by using your IP address when you visit our site or use our app.

In addition, we use **cookies** that are stored in your browser when you visit our website (more details below).

When you create a user account:

When creating a user account on our site or app you may be asked to enter your **e-mail address, a password and a username**. We may also collect your **Facebook ID** if you decide to register or sign in using your Facebook account. You may however visit or use Memedroid anonymously, although some of the features require user registration.

When you contact us:

We collect your **IP address** , **email address** and the **name** you provide us with when contacting us through our contact form.

Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your device's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information). We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, to get anonymous usage statistics and for advertising purposes.

Mostly all major web browsers provide you with features to configure, clear or disable cookies. Generally this can be easily done in the settings menu, but the procedure may vary among browsers. You can remove the cookies from Memedroid whenever you want, but please note that you may have to sign in when you visit the site again because we use cookies to keep you logged in. Except for that everything else will work just fine.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1. **To personalize your experience** (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).

  2. **To improve our website and app** (we continually strive to improve our website/app offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).

  3. **To improve customer service** (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).

  4. **For data analytics** to measure the performance and functioning of Memedroid.

  5. **For security purposes and access control.**

  6. **To show you relevant and personalized ads.**

Who manages your information here?

Memedroid is managed by [Novagecko](http://www.novagecko.com/), a company based in Spain.

For how long do we keep your information?

Unless otherwise requested by you we may keep some of the collected information indefinitely, while other data is deleted when it expires after some inactivity time.

Your information is yours.

The GDPR gives EU individuals rights to their personal data. Whether you are a EU citizen or not we believe you deserve the right to:

  1. Request access to the data we store about you.

  2. Request updates/changes to your personal data.

  3. Request the deletion of your personal data.

  4. Request we limit our collection and use of your personal data.

If you have any request related with your information and your rights above please contact us.

How to remove your user account?

Although we'd be sad to se you leave you can delete your Memedroid account when you want, just contact us requesting the deletion. Please keep in mind that you may be asked to update your password at Memedroid or to mail us from the email address that you used to register your account to confirm its ownership.

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. For example we use HTTPS to transfer your information and we encrypt sensitive data like passwords before storing it.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential and to comply with the privacy laws and regulations. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

This is a list of the **trusted parnerts** we may share your information with, as long as they agree to keep it confidential and to comply with the privacy laws and regulations. You can click on each one of them to review their privacy policies:

  1. [Google Analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

  2. [Google Admob](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

  3. [Google+](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

  4. [Google Ads](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites)

  5. [Other Google services](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

  6. [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php)

  7. [Twitter Mopub](https://www.mopub.com/legal/privacy/)

  8. [Fabric](https://fabric.io/terms)

  9. [Amazon Ads](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496)

  10. [Fyber](https://www.fyber.com/legal/privacy-policy/)

  11. [Tappx](https://www.tappx.com/en/privacy-policy/)

  12. [Embi-Media](http://embi-media.com/privacy-policy.pdf)

  13. [Adview](https://adview.online/policy)

  14. [Sendgrid](https://sendgrid.com/policies/privacy/)

  15. [Vidoomy](http://www.vidoomy.com/)

  16. [Maple Media](http://maplemedia.io/privacy)

  17. [Smaato](https://www.smaato.com/privacy/)

Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website and app at www.memedroid.com/tos

Your Consent

By using our site and/or app, you consent to this privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at www.memedroid.com/contact
